Bri Pepper

Phone: (217) 577-3065 | Email: bripepr@gmail.com | Denver, CO

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/bri-pepper/

Portfolio: www.bripepper.design

UX/UI Designer with a background in the arts, pastry design, and healthcare. Certificate in UX/UI Design from the University of Denver with skills in User Research, Visual Prototyping & Wireframes, User Interface. Strengths in design, creative thinking, critical thinking, teamwork, designing and building projects based on the design process: Empathy, Define, Ideate, Prototype, Test.

Technical Skills

User Research, User Interviewing, Persona Creation, Storyboarding, Heuristic Evaluation, User Flows, Task Flows, Journey Mapping, Value Proposition, Card Sorting, Sketching, Wireframing and Prototyping, User Interface, Style Guides, Color Theory, A/B Testing, Presenting Case Studies

Projects

Peeps For Pets | User Experience Researcher/Designer/User Interface Designer https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1htEdjif_JPe3IV2F5_eaRKxtoO-TRrUE2B8rdykKS9Y/edit?usp=sharing
This project was focused on designing an app that pairs potential pet owners with potential pets based on their personality traits and lifestyles; reducing the rate in which pets are returned to shelters.

 Skills | Technologies Used: User Research (Interviews, Surveys) Analyzed Data (Sorted Notes, Miro, FigmaJam) Utilized Research Methods (Persona Creation, User Flows, Storyboarding) Prototyping & Wireframing (Figma, FigJam), User Testing/Usability Testing

A Little Help Redesign | User Experience Researcher/Designer/User Interface Designer

https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1FJiOmrxa-rTuj_eSH-RNECVLrUiaoQVf/edit?usp=sharing&ouid=106962949468
686387652&rtpof=true&sd=true

The goal of this project was to redesign the website of "A Little Help," a volunteer website to help eldery individuals with daily tasks, so that it was accessible and functional for the User.

 Skills | Technologies Used: User Research (Interviews, Surveys), Stakeholder Interviews, Analyzed Data, Utilized Research Methods, Prototyping & Wireframing, User Testing/Usability Testing, Accessibility Testing, Figma, FigJam, Miro

Nourish | User Experience Researcher/Designer/User Interface Designer

https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1sKQusaxX6htT8X8N2D4hr-NcApbdUcdI7BNnN-NJctU/edit?usp=sharing

This project was centered on designing a sustainable shopping app where Users could find sustainable products on one platform from their favorite stores.

 Skills | Technologies Used: User Research (Interviews, Surveys) Analyzed Data, Utilized Research Methods, Prototyping & Wireframing, User Testing/Usability Testing, Front End Development, Figma, FigJam, Miro

Work Experience

ZimmerBiomet | Remote/CO

August 2022 - Present

Customer Service Representative

- Demonstrated resourcefulness by finding creative solutions to complex issues, optimizing processes and improving overall efficiency
- Utilized an invoicing system to accurately process and track invoices, ensuring timely payments and maintaining financial records.
- Effectively communicated with team members and facilities to coordinate tasks, resolve issues, and ensure smooth workflow
- Demonstrated strong multitasking abilities by managing and prioritizing multiple tasks simultaneously, meeting deadlines consistently
- Successfully met end-of-day and end-of-week deadlines for various projects, ensuring timely completion and delivery
- Maintained a positive and proactive attitude, approaching challenges with a can-do mindset and a willingness to learn and adapt

Cosmo's Dog Bakery & Pet Supplies | Wheat Ridge, CO

July 2021 - August 2022

Customer Service Associate

- Assists customers, conduct research on products + nutrition
- Correcting inventory in Square POS to have an accurate count of products to help the manager with ordering products and see what products are selling well or not selling well
- Helping to increase the number of new customers a day from 1 new customer a day to an average of 5+
 new customers a day with friendly service and encouragement to shop for quality products
 increasing
 sales almost 3 times what it was in the past year

The Yum Factory | Quincy, IL

April 2018 - March 2019

Cake Designer/Bakery Manager

- Planned out orders for the week, assigned each project a timeline during the week to be completed to
 ensure orders were always ready by deadline
- Designed orders based on customer wants/needs resulting in unique products that made the business competitive and gain attention from new customers
- Became a highly requested designer for pastries and praised for ability to make custom designs as close as possible to customers ideas/images
- Communicated efficiently with Owner and other employees so that there was a smooth process for both employees/customers

Education

Certificate, UX/UI January 2022

University of Denver

Associate of Arts May 2015

John Wood Community College